peachandlily.com 2017-06-06

# PRIVACY - Peach & Lily

**Introduction**

Thank you for visiting the Peach and Lily website. Peach and Lily, Inc. (“Peach and Lily,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) is committed to protecting your privacy.

We at Peach and Lily created this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) because we know that you care about how information you provide to us is used and shared.  This Privacy Policy relates to the information collection and use practices of Peach and Lily in connection with our website located at **[www.peachandlily.com](http://www.peachandlily.com/) **(the “Site”), and the Service.

By visiting our Site and/or using our Service, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying Terms of Use. Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Use.

**Information We Collect    **

We do not collect any personal information from you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. The information that we may collect on the Site allows us to improve your shopping experience by catering to your personal preferences.

When you sign up to become a Registered User, you will be asked to provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, email address, postal address, credit card and other payment related information. In this Privacy Policy, we refer to all of this information as “Personal Information.”

Like most web sites, we use automatic data collection technology when you visit our Site to record information that identifies your computer, to track your use of our Site, and to collect certain basic information about you and your surfing habits. This information includes information about your operating system, your IP addresses, browser type and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, keywords, date and time, amount of time spent on particular pages, what sections of a website you visit, and similar information concerning your use of the Site and the Service (the “Usage Information”). 

We may collect this Usage Information by using cookies. Cookies are small packets of data that a web site stores on your computer’s hard drive so that your computer will “remember” information about your visit. You can reject cookies by following the directions provided in your Internet provider’s “help” file.  If you reject cookies, you may still visit the Site, but may not be able to use some areas of the Site and/or the Service.

We do not collect personally identifying information in this way, but if you’ve provided us with personally identifying information we may associate that information with the information that is collected automatically. Automatic data collection may be performed on our behalf by our services providers.

**How We Use Your Information**

We may use your Personal Information and the Usage Information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy and the context of our relationship with you. We will use the personally identifying information collected on this Site for the following purposes:

  1. To respond to your requests and to provide you with the Service;
  2. To respond to your inquiries and contact you about changes to this Site;
  3. To send you notices (for example, in the form of e-mails, mailings, and the like) regarding products or services you are receiving, and for billing and collection purposes;
  4. For any other purposes disclosed at the time the information is collected or to which you consent; and
  5. As otherwise specifically described in this Privacy Policy.

We may also use your information to improve our Site, and may use cookies and other information to enable us to customize your user experience. 

We may also share personal information, demographic information, and purchase history that you provide to Peach and Lily with our strategic partners, such as suppliers and distributors, in order to select the best products for you and our customers. Any strategic partners that are given access to your personal information is contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality of the information shared with them and to strictly use the information to perform the services that we ask them to provide to us and you.

We may provide aggregate statistics, which do not include personal information, about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related Site information to reputable third party vendors. 

We, like many businesses, sometimes hire other companies to perform certain business-related functions.  Examples include mailing information, maintaining databases, hosting services, and processing payments.  When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.  We require such third parties to maintain the confidentiality of such information and use such information only as necessary to provide us with designated services.

If we or all or substantially all of our assets are acquired, we expect that the information that we have collected, including personally identifying information, would be transferred along with our other business assets.

We may disclose Personal Information and Usage Information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required by law, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose Personal Information and the Usage Information when we have reason to believe that someone is or may be causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of this Site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

**How We Protect Your Information**

We take commercially reasonable steps to protect the Personal Information and the Usage Information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Please understand, however, that no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to and from us over the Internet. ****

**Accessing and Modifying Account Information**

You may update the information that is stored in your user account in by visiting www.peachandlily.com or by e-mailing us at info@peachandlily.com

Your Choices:

If you wish to stop receiving promotional e-mails, you may do so through your user account at www.peachandlily.com or by e-mailing [info@peachandlily.com](mailto:info@peachandlily.com) with “Unsubscribe” in the subject header.  You may also choose to unsubscribe from our emails by following the instructions in the bottom of the email.

**Links**

This Site may contain content, services, advertising and other materials that link to web sites operated by third parties.  We have no control over those other sites, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to them. 

**Important Notice to Non-U.S. Residents**

The Site and the Service are operated in the United States.  If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States.  By using the Service and/or providing us with any information, you consent to this transfer. 

**Children    **

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13 through the Service.  If you are under 13, please do not give us any Personal Information.  We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide Personal Information through the Service without their permission.  If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to us, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**       

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy.  We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and will post any changes on the Site as soon as they go into effect.  By accessing the Site or using the Service after we make any such changes to this Privacy Policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes.  Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

**How to Contact Us   **

If you have questions or suggestions about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at info@peachandlily.com with “PRIVACY POLICY” in the subject line.
